[{"answer": "That's sort of a misnomer.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "When that happens a business like yours tends to do well?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "People still want to sell then you can get rid of it?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "I mean it's everybody, especially our store.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "I mean who comes in your store?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "People don't realize, most billionaires actually pretty cheap.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Why the billionaire come to a pawnshop?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "That happens actually a lot.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "I know there must be a lot of surprises, but when you look back what have been the moments, you go, wow, when somebody brought something in that's really knocked your socks off?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "This is actually the battle plan for Iwo Jima, is that right?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "It was a person who's father had been on Iwo Jima.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Who brought this in?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, this was a few years ago.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "How did you assess the value?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "I think it was right around $3500, something like that.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "But do you remember even the ballpark?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "$8,000 or an Iwo Jima plan, I'll take the eight grand.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "So eight grand, it's coming off the wall, right?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Yes, I think his story was basically that he -- you know, he got injured, wasn't able to compete in 2000 and was doing some other things.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "So do you remember his story?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "That's a very difficult thing because they rarely if ever get on the market.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "How do you quantify an Olympic medal?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "So what -- do you remember what you paid him for it?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "So he'll never get them back?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "It's sad.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Sad, isn't it?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "One of the things is a pawn broker with a heart is usually a pawn broker out of business.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "-- is the lesson you handed down to your son, you can't afford to get emotionally involved?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Is there anything you would turn down?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "We won't take any German World War II items.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "Have you ever turned anything down?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "You know, I won't do it.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "I mean just anything in that area.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Is there any other sort of thing you just feel strongly you wouldn't want to be party to?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "It's a real easy one.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "And I suppose the obvious question, what is the most expensive thing you've ever bought?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, every day.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "So do people actually walk in with gold bars?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "I can't remember what it was, I just remember we gave him 500 grand for it.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "What's the biggest -- what's the biggest chunk of gold you've ever had to deal with?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "$500,000?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Actually, in our shop, it's weird.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "And what is the -- if you're smart what is the markup if you move quickly on something like that?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "On that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "I mean, it's a lot of people I don't understand who are in business will say, I'll never do that for 1 percent.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "And is that -- is that the attitude and strategy really?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, you have to -- I mean, it's business.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Take the cash when you can?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "It's a tough struggle, you know, I mean, because you're always wanting to buy stuff, you know it's tough to sell the stuff.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "The worst thing for you is a fully stocked store presumably?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "I think it would be worth a little bit more on you.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "I have a few dodge -- I mean, I -- here's my BlackBerry, I mean, given that it's been owned by me, is it worth more or less than if it hadn't been owned by me?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "God, it is a BlackBerry.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "What kind of markup?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "What do you say to them?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "I think you're right in that -- in that instant.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "I mean surely your natural leaning would be toward the guy that believes the same that you do?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "I think they're both -- I think they're both amazing men.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Who's more charismatic to you?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I will definitely be voting.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Will you be voting?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Well, here's the thing, Piers.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "What are you?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Do you think it's wrong in modern-day America that someone like Mitt Romney, who's made hundreds of millions of dollars and, you know, probably not quite as much as you have, Joel, but he's done OK for himself, but -- that he gets lambasted for his success, lambasted for making that money, that somehow it's become a bad thing to be rich and successful in America?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I'm -- here I go again, but I'm for mercy.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "You must feel offended when you hear him say something like that, don't you?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "I've done four.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "How many books have you done?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "And how many tens of millions of copies have you sold?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's hope the big part of the ministry is that, you know, and we face difficulties, too.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "How do you convince them to take your lead?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "You know, I didn't because, Piers, the foundation of our faith is based out of Israel.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Did you worry about dipping your toe there into a very hot political situation?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Let's see --", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Is he into this P90X thing?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "No, he works out.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "No, I don't work out every day.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Every day?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know if I can give them advice.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "When people go to vote now, at the -- in November, what is the key message you would -- if you were, perhaps, Barack Obama and Mitt Romney here and you wanted them to declare things, what do you want them to declare, truthfully, to the electorate, to make a decision about them?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Well, I would love for it to, but it seems like as long as I can remember, it's always happened.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Do you think it's just poison?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Oh, I'd love it to stop.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Would you like it to stop?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "That's a lot to assume.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Are you or not -- are you not?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "That's a lot to assume, brother.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Let me ask you a direct question.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Where do you get your facts?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "I don't know what that -- what that is.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Are you or have you ever been a liberal?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "A lot.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "How often do you agree with him about any political issue?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "A lot.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "How often do you disagree with him?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm a conservative.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Are you a conservative?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I would categorize Kenny as an independent, actually, a really --", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Would you -- would you categorize him as more of a liberal?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Do you vote?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "I think everybody should vote.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Do you vote?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "I've always voted for the best person, what -- the one that -- that moved me, that I felt would inspire me and would inspire everything else around me.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Who do you vote for normally?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "I don't think that's proper for you to even ask that.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Did you vote for Obama?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "No, I don't -- I don't think it's proper for you to ask that.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I really don't.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Ladies and gentlemen, Piers Morgan received a hug.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Why do I feel I'm losing control of this interview?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Probably.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "My god, is that the first time anyone has hugged you in your life?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "I love CNN, by the way.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "You see what I'm talking about?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Well, I can tell you that the issues that we hear, we -- you know, we tour like crazy, 60 some odd cities this year all over the United States.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Harking who you actually vote for to one side, what are the issues that you really are divided over, would you say?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "I mean if you're asking me that, I think a businessman does, because a businessman creates jobs.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Who do you think would do a better job with America in relation purely to jobs come the next presidential election?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "Well, I think that it's up to each of us.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "Kenny?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "Well, in my home, there on our family farm, seven generations of my family has been on this -- stewarded at this farm in Virginia.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "Because I want them to understand the safety of it.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "But a number of your family went to Virginia Tech, right?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "Let me explain why I hate it.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Why do you hate it?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "Now see, I find that --", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "I mean are you going to outlaw alcohol and cars?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "You would shoot them dead?", "qSentId": 754}, {"answer": "-- keep your limey Brit nose out of it.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "But how do you think you could tighten the laws up?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "Is the total murder rate that different?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "I think that you've got to bring in new gun laws which prohibit the purchase of assault weapons, for example; the purchase of 6,000 rounds of ammunition on the Internet, as that Colorado assassin was able to get perfectly legally.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 788, "question": "What would you -- what would you suggest, Piers?", "qSentId": 787}, {"answer": "I know what a hillbilly is.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 815, "question": "Do you know what a hillbilly is, Piers?", "qSentId": 814}, {"answer": "I wanted to -- I wanted to hire his speechwriter, quite frankly.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 854, "question": "It was an amazing moment, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 853}, {"answer": "I actually feel totally responsible for where he's at.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 867, "question": "Is that what you want to see?", "qSentId": 866}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120923pmt", "aSentId": 908, "question": "What, 30 years?", "qSentId": 907}]